Ramil Assanov

Frontend Developer

+77073890921

aramille@googlemail.com

Work experience

October 2020 — present Citix (BBV)

Almaty, citix.me

Frontend-developer

Development and redesign of admin panel.

- HTML
- CSS
- Angular 10
- Bootstrap
- JS
- jQuery

June 2019 — June 2020

Qara Film Festival

Almaty, qarafilmfest.kz/

Frontend-developer

Development and maintenance of website, content, design.

June 2019 — June 2020

Rocket Firm

Almaty, rocketfirm.com

Frontend-developer

Development and maintenance of websites and presentations for our clients. Home Credit Bank, Bacchus, Batyr Foundation, Nestle, Glo, Deutsch-Kazakh University, Sanofi

Technologies:

- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- Grid
- JS
- React
- Bootstrap
- Gulp
- · Responsive, adaptive

European Backpackers Hostel Almaty

August 2017 — June 2019

October 2015 — June 2017

"Orda" cafe and "Tapanan" flat bread bakery

Almaty

Founder, chef

- Cooking, preps, developing and adding new dishes along with other cooks
- Staff Training and Management (cafe staff and bakers)
- Accounting, groceries, food and bread delivery, working with supermarkets and grocery shops

Education

2018 **Decode.kz**

Almaty

Front-end development

2008-2011 Coventry University

Coventry, UK

Bachelor Degree in Art and Design, Fine Art

Key skills

Languages Russian — Native

English — C2 — Proficiency Kazakh — A1 — Basic German — A1 — Basic

Skills

HTML CSS Sass Bootstrap Responsive JavaScript ReactJS jQuery Gulp npm Git Adobe Photoshop

Additional information

About me

I have a bachelor degree from Coventry University in Fine Arts. I speak English and Russian fluently and learning German. I love to travel, cooking, meeting new people, art and web development. In 2017 I opened a hostel in my hometown Almaty. Since 2018 while working in hostel I started learning frontend development and a year later I started working in Rocket Firm. I'm planning to move to Berlin in few months to reunite with my partner.

My Portfolio website:

https://ramilassanov.github.io/